https://youtu.be/58mRwayDsyw
wermarter
SPEAKER: Hello, in this video, we're
Trong video này,
going to see how to open a Databricks Community Edition
ta sẽ tìm hiểu cách tạo tài khoản
account.
Databricks Community Edition.
It all starts by visiting http://databricks.com.
Đầu tiên, ta vào http://databricks.com
We then click "Try Databricks for Free"
Và click "Try Databricks for Free"
or click on the Sign Up link on the top right corner.
hoặc chọn "Sign Up" ở góc trên bên phải.
The Community Edition is provided for free
Bản Community Edition hoàn toàn miễn phí
and has all the computer [? server ?] resources we
và có đầy đủ tài nguyên [máy chủ]
need to complete this course.
ta cần để hoàn thành khoá học này.
We click Sign Up.
Bạn chọn "Sign Up".
We'll end up with a signup form that looks like this.
Ta sẽ có một trang đăng kí như thế này.
Should be easy to complete it and then click Sign Up.
Sau khi hoàn tất thông tin, ta chọn Sign Up.
You then have to read the Terms of Service
Kế tiếp, bạn phải đọc "Terms of Service"
and scroll down and click Agree.
hoặc lăn chuột xuống dưới và nhấn "Agree".
A few seconds later, you will receive a confirmation email
Vài giây sau, bạn sẽ nhận email xác nhận
on your email account.
trên tài khoản email đã điền vào.
As soon as you receive this email,
Sau khi nhận được mail này,
you can click on the link provided to verify your email.
bạn cần click vào link xác nhận email của mình.
Then, you will see the Databricks Community Edition
Và hiện ra một trang "Log in"
login form.
của Databricks Community Edition.
You can always get back in the space
Bạn cũng có thể đăng nhập lại
by going to community.cloud.databricks.com.
bằng link "community.cloud.databricks.com".
Then, you fill in the email and the password you chose before,
Nhập vào email và password
and you click Sign In.
và click "Sign in".
Congratulations, you just logged in on your Databricks account.
Xin chúc mừng, bạn đã đăng nhập vào tài khoản Databricks của mình.